<resources>
    <string name="exception_can_not_find_token">%1$s:\nToken not found, please pair with the robot again</string>
    <string name="exception_cancel_manual">%1$s:\nThe task was manually canceled, please do not operate the robot from multiple devices simultaneously!</string>
    <string name="exception_check_charge_point_count_error">Detected %1$s charging points, with a total of %2$d. To ensure proper machine reorientation, please remove excess charging points.</string>
    <string name="exception_check_charge_point_position_error">%1$s:\nDetected a large position deviation between the charging points marked in automatic route mode (web - marking page) and fixed route mode (navigation route page). Please ensure the charging points are marked at the same position in both modes to ensure proper machine reorientation.</string>
    <string name="exception_check_more_than_one_enter_elevator_point">Detected %1$d enter elevator points</string>
    <string name="exception_check_more_than_one_inside_elevator_point">Detected %1$d inside elevator points</string>
    <string name="exception_check_more_than_one_leave_elevator_point">Detected %1$d leave elevator points</string>
    <string name="exception_check_more_than_one_waiting_elevator_point">Detected %1$d waiting elevator points</string>
    <string name="exception_current_activity_not_support_online_task">%1$s:\nThe current screen of the robot does not support online tasks. Make sure the robot application is on the main screen</string>
    <string name="exception_current_map_not_in_legal_map_list">%1$s:\nThe currently used map is not available. Please check:\n\t1. Whether the map name is set to the floor number;\n\t2. Whether points are marked on the map;</string>
    <string name="exception_current_task_mode_not_support_response_task_during_task_executing">%1$s:\\nThe robot does not support responding to tasks from the mobile end while executing call-back, recharge, or return tasks</string>
    <string name="exception_decrypt_failed_please_repair">%1$s:\nFailed to parse data, please repair the pairing with the robot</string>
    <string name="exception_device_offline_cannot_get_point">%1$s:\nThe device is offline, unable to query points</string>
    <string name="exception_device_offline_cannot_start_task">%1$s:\nThe device is offline, unable to start the task</string>
    <string name="exception_emergency_stop_down_cannot_start_task">%1$s:\nThe emergency stop switch of the robot has been pressed, unable to start the task</string>
    <string name="exception_executing_again_switch_opened_in_route_task">%1$s:\nThe robot is currently executing a route task, and the switch for repeating route tasks is turned on, so it cannot respond to this task!</string>
    <string name="exception_get_route_failed">%1$s:\nFailed to get the route, please check if there is a route on the robot side and if points have been added to the route</string>
    <string name="exception_is_lifting">%1$s:\nThe robot is currently performing a lift action and cannot execute the task, please try again later</string>
    <string name="exception_json_syntax_exception">%1$s:\nFailed to parse data, please check if the data sent from the mobile end is abnormal</string>
    <string name="exception_last_task_abnormal_finish">%1$s:\nThe last task ended abnormally, unable to respond to this task. Please check the robot and try again</string>
    <string name="exception_lift_model_not_reset">%1$s:\nThe robot\'s lift module is detected as not reset, unable to execute the task</string>
    <string name="exception_loaded_success_map_illegal">%1$s:\nData loaded successfully, but the map name is invalid. Please set the map name to the corresponding floor number</string>
    <string name="exception_map_not_legal">%1$s:\nDetected that map %2$s is illegal:</string>
    <string name="exception_mapping">%1$s:\nThe robot is in mapping mode and cannot execute tasks. Please try again later</string>
    <string name="exception_no_cache_points">%1$s:\nFailed to get points. Please note that the online task mode uses points cached locally on the robot. Make sure to retrieve points on the robot at least once</string>
    <string name="exception_no_enter_and_leave_point">Please calibrate points of type [waiting point] and [exit point] at the elevator entrance</string>
    <string name="exception_no_enter_point">Please calibrate a point of type [waiting point] at the elevator entrance</string>
    <string name="exception_no_inside_point">Please calibrate a point of type [boarding point] inside the elevator</string>
    <string name="exception_no_leave_point">Please calibrate a point of type [exit point] at the elevator exit</string>
    <string name="exception_not_choose_charging_point_map">%1$s:\nIt was detected that the map containing the charging pile was not selected, unable to execute the task. Please go to the robot and select a map with the charging pile before starting the task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_choose_production_point_map">%1$s:\nIt was detected that the map containing the production point was not selected, unable to execute the task. Please go to the robot and select a map with the production point before starting the task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_find_map">%1$s:\nUnable to find valid map data. Please check the robot’s map first.</string>
    <string name="exception_not_found_points">%1$s:\nCannot find the following points: %2$s, unable to start the task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_found_route">%1$s:\nRoute not found, unable to execute route task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_charge_point">%1$s:\nThe charging pile is not marked, please mark the points correctly before starting the task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_charge_point_and_product_point">%1$s:\nThe charging pile and production points are not marked, please mark the points correctly before starting the task</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_charge_point_in_mark_point_page">%1$s:\nDetected that no charging point was marked in automatic route mode (web - marking page). To ensure proper use of the machine’s automatic reorientation function, please mark the charging point in the same position in automatic route mode as in fixed route mode.</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_elevator_point">%1$s:\nMissing points on floor %2$s:</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_enter_elevator_point">Enter elevator point not marked</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_inside_elevator_point">Inside elevator point not marked</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_leave_elevator_point">Leave elevator point not marked</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_path">%1$s:\nIt was detected that there are no fixed routes connected in the current map. Please check the map</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_path_with_maps">%1$s:\nIt was detected that there are no fixed routes connected in the map [%2$s]. Please check the map</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_point">%1$s:\nNo valid points marked. Please mark the points first.</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_product_point">%1$s:\nProduct point not marked. Please correctly mark the points before starting the task.</string>
    <string name="exception_not_mark_waiting_elevator_point">Waiting elevator point not marked</string>
    <string name="exception_not_support_elevator_mode">%1$s:\nThe current task mode does not support elevator control</string>
    <string name="exception_param_error">%1$s:\nParameter error, please check if the data sent from the mobile end meets the specifications</string>
    <string name="exception_please_choose_inside_network">%1$s:\nPlease choose the internal network first.</string>
    <string name="exception_please_choose_inside_network_and_outside_network">%1$s:\nPlease choose the internal network and outside network first.</string>
    <string name="exception_please_choose_outside_network">%1$s:\nPlease choose the outside network first.</string>
    <string name="exception_power_low_cannot_start_task">%1$s:\nThe robot\'s battery is too low to start the task</string>
    <string name="exception_robot_ac_charging">%1$s\nThe robot is currently charging using the adapter and cannot execute the task</string>
    <string name="exception_self_checking">%1$s, The robot is currently undergoing self-checking, please wait...</string>
    <string name="exception_task_executing">%1$s:\nThe robot is executing a task, please wait for the robot to be idle before resending the task</string>
    <string name="exception_task_will_start">%1$s:\nThe robot is preparing to execute another task and cannot respond to this task. Please wait for the robot to be idle and resend the task</string>
    <string name="exception_unbound_button">Unbound button: %1$s</string>
    <string name="text_auto_model">Automatic Route Navigation Mode</string>
    <string name="text_fix_model">Fixed Route Navigation Mode</string>
    <string name="text_start_task">%1$s:\nThe robot starts executing the task</string>
    <string name="text_will_start_task">%1$s:\nThe robot will start the task soon</string>
</resources>